ian.com 2018-09-02

# EAN Privacy Policy - Expedia Affiliate Network

Your browser is out-of-date and some features of this website may not display correctly. [Find out more.](http://outdatedbrowser.com/)

Below you will find the updated Privacy Policy for Expedia Affiliate Network (EAN), which applies to any information provided or collected through this EAN  website and/or any application on a social media or other website  each of which are provided by EAN 160 Greentree Drive, Suite 101, Dover, Delaware 19904.    

We value your trust, and make it a high priority to ensure the security and confidentiality of the personal information you provide to us. Please read this policy to learn about our privacy practices. 

  * What information we collect from you 
  * How we use your information 
  * With whom we share your information 
  * How you can access and/or correct your information 
  * Your choices with respect to the collection and use of your information 
  * Cookies and other technologies 
  * How we protect your information 
  * External links 
  * Transfer of personal information outside your country 
  * Changes to this Privacy Policy 
  * How you can contact us 

**What information we collect from you**

_In General_. We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way. This includes information that can identify you (“personal information”), including your first and last name, email addresses and company. 

_Information from Other Sources_. We automatically collect some information about your computer when you visit this website. For example, we will collect your IP address, Web browser software (such as Firefox, Safari, or Internet Explorer), and referring website. 

**How we use your information**

If you agree, we will send you information about EAN and the benefits of becoming an EAN partner. 

Please review “Your choices with respect to the collection and use of your information” below. 

**With whom we share your information**

With your consent, we may share your information with the following entities: 

  * Social media providers and analytics platforms – We will only share anonymous information in order to assess the performance of our site.  When you access certain social media features through our website such as LinkedIn advertising, you are sharing information with the social media provider and the information you share will be governed by their privacy policies (including that we may access such information via the social media provider). You may be able to modify your privacy settings for these social media providers. Please consult the privacy policy of the relevant social media provider for further information. 

We also may share your information: 

  * In response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases we reserve the right to raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us. 
  * When we believe it is appropriate to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of our company, this website or our Apps, our customers, or others; and in connection with our Terms of Service and other agreements. 
  * Your information can be updated by completing an embedded website form. New submissions tied to the same email address will update your existing contact record. 

**Cookies and other technologies**

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or mobile device when you visit almost all websites. Cookies do not generally recognise you personally and are not harmful to your computer or mobile device. They are used by websites you visit in order to improve your experience on the website, to provide us with analytics information that will help us improve our website generally, and to collect information about travel destinations of interest to you so that you may see travel ads more relevant to you. 

For instance, we use cookies on our site to allow you to login without having to type your login name each time. Other cookies help us to understand what did and didn’t interest you about our website so we can provide you with features that are more relevant and useful to you next time you visit. We and some of our partners also use cookies on our site to measure the effectiveness of advertising on our site and how visitors use our site. 

For more detailed information about the cookies that we and our partners serve through our website, please visit our Cookie Policy. Alternatively, if have any other questions about our use of cookies or other technologies, please email us using our customer service and feedback form and we’ll do our best to help. 

**How we protect your information**

We want you to feel confident about using this website and we are committed to protecting the information we collect. While no website or App can guarantee security, we have implemented appropriate administrative, technical, and physical security procedures to help protect the personal information you provide to us. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they may only do so for permitted business functions. 

**External links**

If any part of this website links you to other sites, those sites do not operate under this Privacy Policy. We recommend you examine the privacy statements posted on those other websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information. 

**Transfer of personal information outside your country**

If you are visiting our website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States, where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country, but please be assured that we take steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Policy. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may update this Privacy Policy in the future. We will notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the email address you provided to us or by placing a prominent notice on our website. 

**How you can contact us**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy please email us or write to us at: 

Email: [EAN Support](mailto:support@ean.com)

160 Greentree Drive,  
Suite 101,  
Dover,  
Delaware  
19904
